<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>DEANDRE.WTF</title>
        <description>the personal website of deandre harris</description>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 22:12:59 +0200</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 22:12:59 +0200</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v4.3.4</generator>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working my ass off. Between taking people’s shifts as they’re thrown at me and trying to get scheduled as much as possible, I’m at that place more than I’d really like to be. I honestly don’t mind being there, it just takes a toll after awhile because I get very little time to myself. Needless to say, days go by; it can be pretty uneventful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are of course many exciting moments, whether they be the result of my being clumsy and too easily amused, good times with my co-workers, or really awesome, non-bitchy customers[1].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday I worked an 8-hour shift. It was very busy throughout the day, I had been operating off of very little sleep[2], and above all my feet were killing me, so I took comfort in knowing that midnight was just around the corner, meaning we’ll finally be able to lock-up, scrub that place from top to bottom, and get our non-ice cream eating asses out of there[3].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just as I was watching the clock, constantly pressing buttons on our register to see that the minutes were in fact passing by, a group of three walked in. Disappointed that my closing routine had been interrupted, I help them. The first thing that struck me was this chick’s unusual inquiries into my age, and how often I work[4]. I was extremely weirded out and thought she was hitting on me, and thus tried to get them out of the store as quickly as possible so I could curl up in a corner and cry. I thought my initial discomfort was very apparent, so I tried to ease the tensions by changing the “subject”-she had the most amazing hat that I fell (am) in love with. The bill was fringed, and it was olive drab, and had little gold studs on one side. I just had to have it, and asked her where she got it from but alas, she had no idea because a friend had sent it to her. For a moment I thought she did it herself and was pretty disappointed when she told me otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the guys she was with I thought was very obnoxious[5], yet I just could not get over the resemblance he bore to someone I’m sure I’ve seen on television or in a movie[6]. He asked for a small scoop of Cherry Garcia but threw it away after taking a bite of it. He decided that he wanted something else. Whatever, I was in no mood to argue[7]. I just thought it was very wasteful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked the third member of the group if I could get something for him, but he kindly declined. I promptly rang them out and wished them a good night. After they left Laura commented in a rather confused tone that the lady looked a lot like Jessica Alba. Me not being one to follow celebrities, I only knew of the name because of a previous conversation with a friend about how hot she is and the subsequent Googling to figure out exactly who she is[8].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was brief speculation between us that maybe they were impersonators until Ashley came up from the basement and did some Googling of her own. Jessica just so happens to be in town filming. Fucking great: I was a complete ass to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/name/nm0004695/&quot;&gt;Jessica Alba&lt;/a&gt;[9].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I wasn’t bothered because of her fame, but more by the fact that she is someone who probably isn’t in the city often much less in our shop and that’s the impression she got and is going to leave with. Way to represent. I just felt terrible all night and it was all I could think about[10].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I worked with Laura again tonight who brought it all back up[11]. Laura actually had a little regret of her own, that is not speaking up about her suspicions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Near close tonight, as I helped a lady with a cake order, a woman and a young man who appeared to be her son walked into the shop. Jenn came up to me and asked if I remembered that WB show &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0410997/&quot;&gt;Jack and Bobby&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, because she thought the guy looked a lot like him. Absent minded, I went into a small yet loud tirade about how I used to love that show because of its concept, but it took a turn that I didn’t like and ended up hating it. Sure enough, that guy turned out to be &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/name/nm0503567/&quot;&gt;Logan Lerman&lt;/a&gt;, who played Bobby McCallister in the aforementioned series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I once again felt terrible. Who else would have such misfortune to blow off Jessica Alba &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; tell off this guy’s work as he stands right in front of you, all in the same weekend. Either Laura or Jenn said to him how funny it was because Jessica was just in the shop the other day. I thought it was very funny that she walked in soon after that was said[12].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time around I was a very good boy. However, it annoys me how star struck people become. They were both pretty patronizing. I don’t understand it. Celebrities should not be placed on a platform because they’re in the spotlight. It was actually kinda gross to see them freak out like they did. I seriously wanted to apologize to both Jessica and Logan, because it was that ridiculous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I have delved into the realm of gossip, this blog will soon return to its regularly scheduled programming. I have a serious backlog of entries and can’t seem to find the time to sit down and write them. It’s also unfortunate because with school being out and me blogging so sporadically, the quality of my writing has diminished significantly. Methinks it’s time to get back in the habit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I love you! Then people wonder why they might get less than great service. It’s not rocket science: respect me and I’ll do the same. Please and Thank You go a long way. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For the past couple of weeks I’ve had some fucked up sleep issues (e.g. not being able to). It concerns me and I really need to get it checked out. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘Cause contrary to popular belief, “the help” have lives too. I need to get out of food service. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The last thing I needed was some crazy creepy psycho stalker lady. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The sleepier I get the less I put up with arrogance and bullshit. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I still can’t place him; clearly I don’t watch either enough. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Like I ever do. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I had to agree, she’s pretty damn hot. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not really an ass, just hurried and creeped out…it was all just a defense mechanism. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;That and her hat. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I was trying to purge regret from memory. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Turns out he’s co-starring in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0790623/&quot;&gt;Bill&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/star-slight</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/star-slight</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Supporters of the [Federal Marriage] amendment say Congress is the right place to set cultural standards, and that traditional marriages are the foundation of healthy societies. Those on this side of the debate draw a connection between nontraditional families, poverty and troubled children.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;— From the Newsvine article &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newsvine.com/_news/2006/06/06/244964-senate-debate-on-gay-marriage-to-continue&quot; title=&quot;Newsvine - Senate Debate on Gay Marriage to Continue&quot;&gt;Senate Debate on Gay Marriage to Continue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Tue 6 June 2006&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate to be a naysayer, but if that’s the case, then look at how far traditional marriages have gotten us. Someone who sees these connections, please, I beg of you!—help me to see them too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More from me soon, I promise.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/senate-debates-gay-marriage</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/senate-debates-gay-marriage</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The other day a woman came into the shop. She asked if she could photograph, and shared with us a brief anecdote about how ours was the first Ben &amp;amp; Jerry’s that she’s been to since she left home or something or another—I don’t know, I zoned out after the first few words. This was super exciting for me on so many levels, and I without hesitation told her to feel free. Pretty bold of me considering I’m not a shift leader or anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it may have been nothing more than courtesy, I’m upset that she felt the need to ask. Why? I couldn’t help but think of the numerous occasions in which she encountered opposition to such a harmless act. Why can’t more people be as accomodating?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/photography-is-not-a-crime</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/photography-is-not-a-crime</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;For no good reason (I’ll go into it at a later time) I’m giving a shot at veganism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me just begin by saying that there is nothing to eat in my house, at all! Yesterday morning I ran over to the corner store to buy wheat bread. I figured I’d atleast be able to make some of those peanut butter and honey sandwiches that I love so much. Before I left for work, I asked my mom if we could go to the grocery store soon so that I can hit the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I don’t consume what my place of work sells, the lure of that which I couldn’t have was tempting. I kept control though and was really proud of myself for it. When I did give in, it was for the sorbets (they’re water-based).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Incredibly hungry, I decided to go to Straub’s during my break, but not before a quick stop to the library for books on veganism. I managed to find one, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0609804898/boihazard-20?tag=boihazard-20&quot; title=&quot;The Voluptuous Vegan: More Than 200 Sinfully Delicious Recipes for Meatless, Eggless, and Dairy-Free Meals&quot;&gt;The Voluptuous Vegan&lt;/a&gt;, which I perused while browsing the aisles at Straub’s (well, before focusing my attention on a very cute stock boy). I walked out of the door with fruit salad and a box of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nabiscoworld.com/Brands/ProductInformation.aspx?BrandKey=WHEATTHINS&amp;amp;Site=1&amp;amp;Product=4400004802&quot; title=&quot;Nabisco Multi-Grain Wheat Thins&quot;&gt;Multi-Grain Wheat Thins&lt;/a&gt;, which I’ve been snacking on in lieu of the pizza that was waiting for me when I got home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That day over, I think I’ve done very well. Let’s see what challenges this one brings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterthought: I was supposed to play tennis with Tyi this morning. Already it’s 4 a.m. What’s the likelihood of that happening? And I’ll be going to Straub’s more often—what was it? Boyd?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/livin-la-vida-vegan-day-1</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/livin-la-vida-vegan-day-1</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a little burned out. Even with school ending I’m still incredibly busy with work. (That, my friends, is the result of asking for more hours.) But, I need the money, or so I tell myself—saving up for school, you know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also in the process of looking for if not another, then a second job. The parking garage next to the library posted the availability of a position, which I will inquire about on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eh, I have a couple of entries drafted, one on graduation and another on that naughtly little four-letter word: &lt;em&gt;oreo&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/im-not-dead</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/im-not-dead</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;To the boy from the Galleria,&lt;br /&gt;
     who was rocking the largest bronzed eagle I’ve ever seen near a crotch,&lt;br /&gt;
     who is one of the few people to pull off camo,&lt;br /&gt;
     and who has the most amazing smile ever,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I apologize. I apologize for making something out of nothing. I overanalyze things: the overwhelming fear of rejection made it impossible to form the words or express the least bit of interest. But you were a sweetheart, I could tell—there was no reason to be afraid. Looking back, the words finally came: “Hey, what’s your name?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it means anything, I looked for you. Hopefully, I’ll run into you again, but judging how things have gone in the past, I shouldn’t set my hopes too high.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/letter-to-a-john</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/letter-to-a-john</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;I happened upon &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.xxlmag.com/mb/index.php?showtopic=25401&quot;&gt;segments&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetgangs.com/movies/hood2hood.html&quot;&gt;Hood 2 Hood&lt;/a&gt;, the so-called “blockumentary” that for some time now I’ve wanted to see. Is it natural to be angry and stupified all while watching this? This is the biggest bunch of BS I’ve ever seen. Not only does it present inaccurate rubbish about what’s “real” in the city, it also perpetuates the negative portrayal of urban America typical of the mainstream media. It’s poorly produced, much like that candy rap heard on Top 40 radio networks. If I were to ever become rich, one of the first things I would do is buy out all of the American media outlets, and fire everybody. It’s either that or something I can’t mention because I wouldn’t want to incriminate myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is anyone with me on this? I am beyond frustrated. Today is Senior Skip Day. I don’t know if there was some class gathering planned, but I do know that I will be at the History Museum and the Art Dimensions gallery downtown, as well as getting some reading done in a park. Feel free to join, you have my number.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/this-is-our-emergency</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/this-is-our-emergency</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;According to Jenn and her mother who’s a nurse, I have the flu. It makes sense, because I have never experienced extreme chills or crippling bodyaches before when sick. &lt;cynicism&gt;Fucking great.&lt;/cynicism&gt; In other news, how bigoted must one be to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.latimes.com/news/nationworld/nation/la-na-christians10apr10,0,6204444.story?coll=la-home-headlines&quot;&gt;sue for the right to be intolerant&lt;/a&gt;? All I can say is Wow.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/flu-right-to-intolerance</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/flu-right-to-intolerance</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a seriously quick update from me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems as if school might as well be over. I rarely go to class, if I have any to go to, and more often than not I arrive late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow is the last day of training for the peer mentoring program. To be honest, I’ve really enjoyed it—I’ve met a wonderful group of people and learned ridiculous amounts of stuff. It has been tiring (having to be up so early and staying still for so long, then having to work afterwards), but I think it’s worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ran my idea for Scoopers Making Change by Mark tonight. He loved it, which is great because now I’m even more excited. I’ve decided that I personally will have no objections to starting school in the spring (I understand and appreciate your concern, Julia. Believe me, the last thing I’m going to do is stay around here.) I’m still going to save for the deposits, then pay those once I can. But it will be nice having a little bit of extra change for my planned trip to Chicago (Pretty Girls Make Graves, et. al.).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recent surge in me being harrassed because of my percieved sexual orientation while walking to and fro bus stops has sparked an interest in matters of race and sexuality. It can be hard enough being gay, but being gay and part of a culture which is known for its hypermasculinity, misogynism, and inherent homophobia certainly makes things more interesting. In the past couple of weeks, I was followed part of the way home by a group of people as well as taunted by yet another on two seperate occasions (these are the more notable). I’m not one to be afraid—as I shared with the group today: I believe that people are generally good—but during these incidents, I was certainly concerned for my safety. I mean really, how much would it have sucked to be bashed in the middle of night only a couple of blocks from home? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rashawnbrazell.com/&quot;&gt;That shit happens&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not really sure where or who to look to, I’m reading Keith Boykin’s &lt;em&gt;One More River to Cross: Black &amp;amp; Gay in America&lt;/em&gt;. It’s quite excellent, I must say. Perhaps I’ll respond to it at a later date, but for now&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good night, and good luck.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/cocoa-royale</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/cocoa-royale</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Bruce opened class (a good half hour late, I want to say) with some insight that I will share. He said, and I paraphrase, that sure, we may want to blow off our few remaining weeks, but everyday has something good to offer, something for you to take from it. Those are some of the wisest words I’ve heard in some time, and he’s totally right. I completely agree with him it’s just that my loathing for Metro causes me to lose sight of such things. I figured rather than waking up pissed at the world that I have to go to school, I’ll wake up pleased that it’s one less day until the end of it. I also think I’ll stop falling asleep in classes, and start doing my homework, which brings me to…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…an assignment that he gave. The prompt is something along the lines of &lt;em&gt;Write about something you’ve learned, contextualized in your childhood&lt;/em&gt;. A very rough paraphrase because honestly, no one knows what exactly the fuck we’re supposed to be writing about. Still, my premise is that my childhood is virtually non-existant because I remember almost nothing about it. (My memory is terrible, if you didn’t catch that.) It’s quite sad, because I often hear people reminiscing on how they did this and went there, yet, I have nothing. I managed to jot down a couple of paragraphs, starting with how my homelife was never typical. There are still so many blanks to fill in: Why, for instance. I’m a firm believer that things happen for a reason—take for example when I found that digital camera lying in the street and contemplated for a week rather or not to return it. I eventually did, after going through all that drama with Kyle taking my CD player right from under me and getting away with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight at work, to my surprise, there was a benefit night for of all organizations my old elementary school. Oh man: Ms. Russel, Ms. Robinson, Ms. Jackson, it was pretty insane. But in some strange way that gave me a bit of guidance which I will follow later on tonight when writing this damn thing. Seeing so many familiar faces, and new faces, was amazing. I secretly miss that place—the good ol’ days, right? (Like I’d know.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve confirmed the dates of IB testing: May 3rd, 4th, and 5th. The beauty in this is that I only have one paper that Friday and it’s in the morning, so with some slick maneuvering, I might be able to make it to Chicago in time to relax a little bit before catching the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.prettygirlsmakegraves.com/&quot;&gt;concert&lt;/a&gt;. I need to check with Wintaye, Meade, and Tyi about this real soon because I seriously want to do this. So it worked out, it seems—no need to skip exams after all. Well, assuming everything else goes accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearly two months after it was dated, I finally recieved my acceptance letter from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.colum.edu/&quot;&gt;Columbia&lt;/a&gt;. Sure, this is great (official) news and all, but with it I realize the pinch that I’m in. I need to come up with $750 for housing and tuition deposits by May 1st. Just now I e-mailed Matt asking for more hours, and I’m expecting a good amount assuming I’m selected to be a queer peer mentor. But I’ve also realized that if worse comes to worse, I may have to defer admission until the spring. Does that suck as much as it sounds? I mean doing so will certainly allow me to save up the much needed cash. I’m just not sure I want to stick around here for much longer than I have to.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/television-rules-the-nation</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/television-rules-the-nation</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
